export const quests = [
    {
      "question_no": 1,
      "question": "What symbol is commonly used to represent a menu or navigation in UI/UX design?",
      "options": [
        "Triangle",
        "Circle",
        "Square",
        "Hamburger icon"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question_no": 2,
      "question": "What is the main consideration in responsive design?",
      "options": [
        "Optimizing the website or application for search engines",
        "Creating a visually attractive interface",
        "Ensuring the product works well on different devices and screen sizes",
        "Minimizing loading times"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 3,
      "question": "Which tool is commonly used for configuration management in DevOps?",
      "options": [
        "Docker",
        "Kubernetes",
        "Ansible",
        "Jenkins"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a common component of an Operations Suite?",
      "options": [
        "Monitoring",
        "Automation",
        "Code repository",
        "Incident management"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 5,
      "question": "What is overfitting in the context of machine learning?",
      "options": [
        "When a model performs well on the training data but poorly on unseen data",
        "When a model performs poorly on both training and unseen data",
        "When a model fails to learn from the training data",
        "When a model performs perfectly on both training and unseen data"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question_no": 6,
      "question": "Which of the following is a feature of Gemini's platform?",
      "options": [
        "Smart contract execution",
        "Decentralised governance",
        "Two-factor authentication",
        "Proof-of-Stake consensus mechanism"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 7,
      "question": "What is a Tensor in TensorFlow?",
      "options": [
        "A high-level programming language",
        "A multidimensional array",
        "A visualization tool",
        "A database management system"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question_no": 8,
      "question": "What does EDA stand for in data analysis?",
      "options": [
        "Estimated Data Aggregation",
        "Exploratory Data Augmentation",
        "Essential Data Analysis",
        "Exploratory Data Analysis"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question_no": 9,
      "question": "Which testing strategy is commonly used in microservices architecture to ensure service isolation?",
      "options": [
        "Integration testing",
        "End-to-end testing",
        "Unit testing",
        "Performance testing"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 10,
      "question": "Which Kubernetes component is responsible for managing containerized applications?",
      "options": [
        "kube-proxy",
        "kubelet",
        "etcd",
        "kube-controller-manager"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question_no": 11,
      "question": "Which technology is commonly used to track the user's head movements in Virtual Reality (VR) experiences?",
      "options": [
        "Accelerometer",
        "GPS",
        "Gyroscope",
        "Barometer"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question_no": 12,
      "question": "What role does machine learning play in AR/VR development with Apple Vision Pro?",
      "options": [
        "It helps in improving gesture recognition accuracy.",
        "It enables real-time translation of virtual text into multiple languages.",
        "It assists in creating lifelike avatars for virtual environments.",
        "It optimizes battery usage for prolonged AR/VR experiences."
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question_no": 13,
      "question": "What does \"hot reload\" mean in the context of Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "Reloading the entire application from scratch",
        "Reloading only the changed parts of the code without restarting the app",
        "Reloading the app after updating the operating system",
        "Reloading the app after a crash"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question_no": 14,
      "question": "What is a \"widget\" in Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "A small application",
        "A graphical element used for constructing user interfaces",
        "A function that performs a specific task",
        "A type of database"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question_no": 15,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid HTTP status code?",
      "options": [
        "200",
        "404",
        "503",
        "1000"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]